{
    "subject": "resource/DJ_Jazzy_Joyce",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "DJ Jazzy Joyce is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9601122140884399,
            "question": "Is DJ Jazzy Joyce American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8938912749290466,
            "question": "Where is DJ Jazzy Joyce from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8858298659324646,
            "question": "How has DJ Jazzy Joyce's upbringing in the United States impacted their career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8689877390861511,
            "question": "Does DJ Jazzy Joyce's music reflect their American background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7320123314857483,
            "question": "What country is DJ Jazzy Joyce associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7209089398384094,
            "question": "Where was DJ Jazzy Joyce raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.676360547542572,
            "question": "What is DJ Jazzy Joyce's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6470620036125183,
            "question": "Is DJ Jazzy Joyce known for representing a specific country in their work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6250283718109131,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about DJ Jazzy Joyce's origins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43519678711891174,
            "question": "What influences might have shaped DJ Jazzy Joyce's musical style due to their origins?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=DJ Jazzy Joyce is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9072_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about DJ Jazzy Joyce's origins?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9072_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is DJ Jazzy Joyce known for representing a specific country in their work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9072_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is DJ Jazzy Joyce's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9072_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9072_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9072_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9072_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9072_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9072_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9072_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9072_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9072_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9072_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9072_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, the answer to the query \"DJ Jazzy Joyce is from United States\" can be evaluated as follows:\n\n* The documents mention that DJ Jazzy Joyce is a native of New York and has performed in many areas across the United States (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9072/re-ranker-msmarco/30.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9072/re-ranker-msmarco/63.txt).\n* The documents also mention that DJ Jazzy Joyce is an American hip hop DJ and producer (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9072/re-ranker-msmarco/30.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9072/re-ranker-msmarco/63.txt).\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about DJ Jazzy Joyce being an American hip hop DJ and producer, which supports the statement that she is from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}